Guide to the Philip Wagner papers, (ca. 1934-1997)
Wagner, Philip papers, (ca. 1934-1997)
- Series V. Photographs
  - Philip, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 88-90)
    "Original Filter" [negatives - in very poor condition]
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 91)
    barrels and tubing ("These are very old winery pictures.")
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 93)
    Becker-Guyer Stemer, Philip
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 94)
    shipment arrival (Boordy), large pieces
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 95)
    large pieces (Boordy)
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 96-99)
    Jocelyn demonstrating Cristal Filter Drum Liner
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 100)
    tractor with sprayer attachment
  - Bottles and bottling machine (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Boordy equipment, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    Crusher
  - Equipment, August 1980 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    Shipment arrival, large pieces
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 103)
    Jocelyn with vinyl fermenter liner
  - Glassware (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Heavy equipment, 1983, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Grape processing and wine making (Box 11, Folder 104)
    barrels and bottles
  - Grape processing and wine making (Box 11, Folder 105)
    workers and vats
  - Grape processing and wine making (negatives) (Box 11, Folder 106)
    barrel, Philip
  - Grape processing and wine making, c. 1910 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    Philip as a child working original basket press
  - Grape processing and wine making, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 108-110)
    Apparatus
  - Grape processing and wine making, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 111-112)
    Boordy harvesting, workers
  - Grape processing and wine making, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    Boordy bottling
  - Grape processing and wine making, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    Boordy barrel and press
  - Grape processing and wine making, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    Mac. Carbonique, T/40 & G-bec, Miller, 4986, 5276
  - Grape processing and wine making, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    Carbonic maceration
  - Places - France (Box 11, Folder 117-121)
    Nancy, Bar le Duc, Paris, Lyon, Pierrefond, Bourbelou, unidentified
  - Places - France (Box 11, Folder 122)
    Lafite, October 1972
  - Unidentified, November 1972 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Benmarl, June 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Places - Italy (Box 11, Folder 123-125)
    Ezio Maria
  - Florence, Lucca, Luigi, Sta. Stefano, Forum?, Sybilla, Ostia (Box 11, Folder 123-125)
  - Places unidentified - France or Italy (Box 11, Folder 126-127)
  - Places - Germany (Box 11, Folder 128)
    Koenig, Riguewihr
  - Places - Boordy (Box 11, Folder 129)
    house and lawn
  - Places - U.S., 1986 (Box 11, Folder 130)
    Raugeley
  - Places - U.S. (Box 11, Folder 131)
    West
  - Places - U.S. (Box 11, Folder 132)
    Central Valley, July 1973 [California?]
  - Places (Box 11, Folder 133)
    unidentified
  - Vine Propagation Nursery (Box 11, Folder 134)
    harvest
  - Vine Propagation Nursery (Box 11, Folder 135)
    fields, working in fields
  - Vine Propagation Nursery, 1952, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    Working in fields
  - Vine Propagation Nursery, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 137-138)
    Planting
  - Vine Propagation Nursery, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    Trench with cuttings (prints and negatives)
  - Vine Propagation Nursery, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 140-142)
    Preparing ground and planting
  - Vine Propagation Nursery, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Vine Propagation Nursery, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 145)
    Alsace pruning, Vezelsy, unidentified
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 146)
    unidentified, Moffett
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 147-150)
    vines and workers spraying vines
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 151-154)
    vines and workers
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 155)
    Boordy from porch, tractor in vineyard
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 156)
    unidentified color transparencies
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 157)
    "There are numerous different varieties. Details can be supplied on any that may interest you. P. W." [color transparencies]
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 158)
    Zinfandel A-25 (color transparency)
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 159)
    J[ocelyn] with plowman in Côte d'Or (prints and color transparencies)
  - Vineyards and vines, October 1952 (Box 11, Folder 160)
    France - Rhine Neuf Brisach (color transparencies)
  - Vineyards and vines, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 161)
    Fall 1953, November 1954
  - Vineyards and vines, September 1955 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    Grapes - N. G. (color transparencies)
  - Vineyards and vines, September 1955 (Box 11, Folder 163)
    Grapes, Lussier
  - Vineyards and vines, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 164-166)
    Unidentified
  - Vineyards and vines, 1965? (Box 11, Folder 167)
    Phylloy or Erinore? off Venice
  - Vineyards and vines, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 168)
    Spring Hammondsport
  - Vineyards and vines, Spring 1972 (Box 11, Folder 169)
    Spring - Foster and Harper
  - Vineyards and vines, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    Spring weed killer, weed killer 3 weeks later, weed killer effect April
  - Vineyards and vines, July 1972 (Box 11, Folder 171-172)
    Snake River
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 11, Folder 173)
    Manor - winter 1972-3
  - Pruning, Phil Carroll (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Double end posts (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Home Ruby - spring 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Vineyards and vines, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    1/2 dead vinifera 5/24/73 - Keuka Lake
  - Vineyards and vines, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Detera [(sp?)] 5/73, same vineyard 5/73
  - Vineyards and vines (negatives) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Dr. Frank's vineyard condition, summer 1977
  - Raugeley (ski lift) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Foreman photos of Audrey, Aug & J[ocelyn] at Lucie Morton's, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Dr. Frank - July, (Ser Spara) #70
  - Boskydel Vineyard, Michigan, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Vineyards and vines (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Manor 7053, 6-7/80
  - Unidentified 8/80, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Vineyards and vines, c. 1980 (Box 12, Folder 6-10)
    Ripping out BX vineyard. Many poor nursery photos. Great shot of Adrian & Peter's youngest. Lunch with Cedar Point people.
  - Vineyards and vines, August 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #1) (Box 12, Folder 12-15)
    "Experimental Miscellany. Wash. Expressway -- Freddie Graebel, Winery"
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #2), November 1958 (Box 12, Folder 16-21)
    "London/Paris" (appears to actually be shots of region around Baltimore and Boordy), Walter Taylor
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #3), November 1958 (Box 12, Folder 22-30)
    France
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #4), 1958 (Box 12, Folder 31-32)
    Christmas plus Sondheim & snaps of JSR, ELI, EVB, CP
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #5), 1958 (Box 12, Folder 33-36)
    Fin Nov. en Arbois, Gander -- office snaps, Christmas, etc.
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #7), 1959 (Box 12, Folder 37-41)
    Primary election (March), Gunpowder, bird Prettyboy, Peter - Anne, H. O./de la Rue
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #8), 1959 (Box 12, Folder 42-45)
    Daisy's wedding, Ratoop (?) - visit, Wroten Island Trip (4/59)
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #9), May-June 1959 (Box 12, Folder 46-47)
    Ann Arbor, Wroten Island (Lou & Willie), chez Dickie, Portsmouth trip
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #10), Summer 1959 (Box 12, Folder 48-50)
    Barbie visit July 4th, Fine Spin planter, Jwo & Betty, Jerry & J at Pine
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #10A), October 1959 (Box 12, Folder 51-55)
    Trip to W., Md. and So. Md. - Dillen, Bennett Crain, Potomac, etc.
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #10B), Spring 1960 (Box 12, Folder 56-57)
    Bottling - Freddie Groebel, Paris - Warsaw - Sunday in Moscow with soldiers
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #11), Spring 1960 (Box 12, Folder 58-59)
    Moscow - Leningrad - Free Market, etc. (contact print and negatives)
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #13): European trip, Spring 1960 (Box 12, Folder 60-63)
    Paris - Côte de Blancs - Saar - Sept Saults - Binn (2nd week of May) good prints Moscow - type Riesling pruning
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #15), June 1960 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    Swariz wedding
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #15), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    Lift-tote, French girls (Charles Farnari, neice, etc.), office flashes, CDI, EVB, ELJ
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #15), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    Cats
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #19), Fall-Winter 1960 (Box 12, Folder 67-69)
    Crisfield, etc., Spring 1961 - party for Frank Beirne, Farnari Dec. D-NY
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #20), Spring-Summer 1961 (Box 12, Folder 70-73)
    Lake Erie Island, Fouruin, etc.
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #21), October 1961 (Box 12, Folder 74-77)
    California
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #22), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 78-79)
    1962 trip
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #23), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 80-84)
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #24), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 85-86)
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #25), May 1962 (Box 12, Folder 87-91)
    Portugal, O porto, etc.
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #26), [1962] (Box 12, Folder 92-94)
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #27), 1962, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 95-98)
    A. A. Thanksgiving, Christmas, Latty visit Fall, Chestnuts November (at Muer), Spring primary of Ruby (May/1963)
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #28), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 99-102)
    Spring through December includes Wroten Island with Freddie's, return trip, Dr. Frank, Dec. photos of Phil
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #29): Christmas 1963-Christmas 1964, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 103-105)
    Visits of Richard Scotts and Françoise Fouruin
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #31), Summer 1965 (Box 12, Folder 106-107)
    Bob & Gwen, Paroissien/Harper dinner, Vintage 1965 snaps J[ocelyn] & Frank Grant
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #32), 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 108-110)
    Christmas 1965, Rockport October 1965, blizzard February 1966, visit to Niagara Falls January 1966
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #33), Summer 1966 (Box 12, Folder 111-113)
    Milan, Vincenza, Ravenna, Venice, also a good print of Jocelyn at home
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #34), July 1966 (Box 12, Folder 114-116)
    Venice, Ravenna, Urbino, Gubbio, Perugia
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #35), July 1966 (Box 12, Folder 117-119)
    Orvieto, Porto Ercola, picnic - Roma
  - Green Photo Box 1 (Roll #36), August 1966 (Box 12, Folder 120-123)
    Aunney, Belloy, Lunder, Solutré, Corcelles, Gwen & Bob's visit (September), Einser & Oleno, loading of Ms. Alondru (cattle ship), visit of Gaunoux father and mother, sister, Gwen's last visit
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #37) (Box 12, Folder 124-128)
    Great Western
  - Christmas 1966 (Box 12, Folder 124-128)
  - Visit to Reston, Va. (Box 12, Folder 124-128)
  - Spring 1967, nursery pictures, summer spraying, September 1966-August 1967 (Box 12, Folder 124-128)
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #38), August-September 1967 (Box 12, Folder 129-134)
    Vinifera hawk flights, Salerski delivery, grape close-ups for catalog
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #39), 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 135-136)
    Vintage 1967 (crusher-stemmer), Sue & the Margot Maques in Fall 1967, Dr. Frank Fall 1967, Miner Vineyard Spring 1968
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #40), August-October 1968 (Box 12, Folder 137-139)
    Pre-vintage, F. S. visit, Anheimer visit, Ch. Gay, Westfield, Rioja
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #41), October 1968 (Box 12, Folder 140-141)
    Lograno, S. Sebastian, Oroissre [sp?], Ghouz
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #42), October 1968-February 1969 (Box 12, Folder 142-143)
    Bordeaux, N. Y. flight, (Sugar Fox) Finger Lakes, March 1 snowstorm
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #43), April-May 1969 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
    Mother, Nursery, Kier's Waterfall, Susan Wolcott, Libby and Hogachy, Kronheim party
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #44), May 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4-8)
    May 19-27, 1969 -- Prosser - Davis - S. F.
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #45), Spring 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9-11)
    Davis (Alley), our vinifera, dedication of HLM house, with Jenny & Ilene, Portsmouth HS, defera vineyard (contact sheet and negatives)
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #46), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12-14)
    October-November, Epernay, Arbois, Morges
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #47), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
    October-November, Sion, Beaujolais, Bearne, London
  - Green Photo Box 2: unidentified, December 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    J, family (?)
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #48): Fall 1969 through Spring 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
    Anita - F. S. wedding, Christmas in Maine, nursery digging - Bogher [sp?], plowing nursery - Foster
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #49), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 20-23)
    Sue's 1970 birthday, Penn Yan visit in spring (including snaps of Greyton Taylor nursery), dead Gold Seal vinifera (summer 1970), beginning to 1970 West Coast trip
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #50), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 24-26)
    Jugoslavia -- Belgrade area and into Sarajevo, October 1970 (a few prints of August 1970 Boordy race meeting, (mm design)
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #51), October 1970 (Box 13, Folder 27-29)
    Jugoslavia -- Sarajevo -- Dubrovnik
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #52), October 1970 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Jugoslavia -- Dubrovnik, Kotor, Slovenia, Lake Bled
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #53), October-November 1970 (Box 13, Folder 31-32)
    Jugoslavia -- Slovenia, Zagreb, Paroissiens in Holyport (with photos of new French winery sign)
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #53a), Summer 1971 (Box 13, Folder 33-36)
    Sam Moore and wife, Prosser, Bill Wolfe, etc.
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #53b), Summer 1971 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    Part of Yukon trip, big birthday for J[ocelyn] in New York
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #54), Fall 1971 (Box 13, Folder 38-39)
    Spain -- Sardana, Javea, Barcelona
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #55), October 1971 (Box 13, Folder 40-41)
    Spain -- Benierulo [sp.?], Tarragara, Miguel Torres - Pruntes (contact sheet and negatives)
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #56), Autumn 1971 (Box 13, Folder 42-44)
    Spain -- René Barbier, Mallorca
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #58), July 1972 (Box 13, Folder 45-48)
    Seattle, Prosser, Victoria
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #59) (Box 13, Folder 49-53)
    Victoria, B. C., July
  - Shots of P. W., etc., August-September, July-September 1972 (Box 13, Folder 49-53)
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #60), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 54-56)
    Europe, October-November 1972
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #61), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 57-58)
    France and England, Roumagousse [sp?]
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #62), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 59-60)
    Wroten Island 1/1/73, party at Pali
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #63), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 61-62)
    Spring through June, Ev spring inflorescences and pruning, Mark Miller Ber M2v1, killed - 6.4c vinifera with Zeke May 1973
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #64): W. Coast July 1973, Napa Valley with Wolcotts, Pasco, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 63-64)
    Also Henri Maire visit & the Clarkes
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #65): December 1973-September 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 65-69)
    Raugeley, Sue, load of posts, Knopf, JS26-205, Vidal 251
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Roll #66): August to Christmas 1974, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 70-74)
    Winery pictures (pressing and racking shelf lots), visit to Walter Taylor, Christmas in Brookline
  - Green Photo Box 2 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    unidentified [could be Spain, Portugal Italy, or Yugoslavia]
  - From Photo Album 1 [labels may refer to entire group of photos on a page, most from negatives in Boxes 1 & 2], 1961, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    Rockport 1965, California 1961 - Benarts
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    Wroten Island 1961
  - Unidentified (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Solon Kelly, ? Sichal 1961, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    snowstorm, unidentified
  - From Photo Album 1, 1964, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 79)
    Winter 1964, winery
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 80-81)
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    Frank Grant, Penny Grant, Lussiers
  - From Photo Album 1, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    Lot '68, San Sebastian '68, Lot No. Cahors
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    truffles in Cahors, Moissac, Loyvano [sp?]
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    Harold
  - Libby Baer (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Central Park, N. Y. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Manor, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    family shots
  - From Photo Album 1, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    Unidentified party, cats
  - From Photo Album 1, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    Family, Hanzelle Winery
  - From Photo Album 1, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    Unidentified, Wroten Island, turkeys
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    at Phelps Ranch, Walter, Martinis
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    meeting at Napa, Wolcott's - Napa, Salverain, at Berringer's, Andy, Maynard M. - Dotty
  - From Photo Album 1, n.d., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    Maynard M., Sonoma, the Mark Millers 1973, the Maires - Sr. & Jr.
  - From Photo Album 1, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    Portsmouth reunion
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    the Sam Moores
  - Louis Martini, California (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Unidentified (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Henri Maire & son - M. Fourcade (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - P says goodbye & Valiant, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - From Photo Album 1, August 1973, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 95)
    Unidentified, family
  - From Photo Album 1, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    Family
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    unidentified [France]
  - From Photo Album 1, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    France - Chambertin, Bearne, Corta Vineyard, East of Mortraux, d'Augeville
  - From Photo Album 1, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    Autun, Rolle (Suisse), Sion, Jura
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    Ricciutti
  - Aveny (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Arbas, Alsmurum, Henri-Minn, Pl. des Vosges, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - From Photo Album 1, 1969, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 101)
    Aveny, Ricciutti vineyard in Aveny, Boordy
  - From Photo Album 1, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    Unidentified party
  - From Photo Album 1, 1971, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 103)
    Unidentified, birthday 1971, family
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    Slovenia, Sarajevo, Dubrovnik, Kator, on way to Split
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    Sardana, Barcelona
  - Panades - (Torres) (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    Carlos
  - Mrs. Bowden, Magdalena, Dom Miguel, Petra (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Peniscola (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    Dubrovnik, Mostar, Sarajevo
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    at Turkish house, Sarajevo
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    Sarajevo, Jerusalem, Nowidad, Zagreb airport, dumping harvest at winery
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    Jugoslavia, Lake Bled
  - From Photo Album 1 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    Kator, Trogir, Maribor
  - From Photo Album 2 [labels may refer to entire group of photos on a page, most prints are from negatives in Boxes 1 and 2], 1971 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    Portugal
  - From Photo Album 2, 1962, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 113)
    7 May 1962
  - From Photo Album 2, May 1962 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    Unidentified, olive oil factory
  - From Photo Album 2, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - From Photo Album 2, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    Christmas, Rangeley
  - From Photo Album 2, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - From Photo Album 2, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    Wroten Island
  - From Photo Album 2, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 119-120)
    New Year's 1973, Wroten Island
  - From Photo Album 2, [1973] (Box 13, Folder 121-122)
    [Wroten Island]
  - From Photo Album 2, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    Weston, unidentified party
  - From Photo Album 2, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    Christmas
  - From Photo Album 2, 1983, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 125)
    Rangeley, Christmas 1983 and 1985
  - From Photo Album 2, 1983, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    Boordy
  - From Photo Album 2, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    Summer, Bonnie & Mungo
  - From Photo Album 2, Spring 1983 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    Spring, Tom's impedimenta
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album (small photo insert)], 1966 (Box 13, Folder 129-130)
    Venice 1966, Milan from Cathedral steps, unidentified
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album (small photo insert)], Spring 1966 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    Riderwood
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 1, July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 132-133)
    Milan, Bergamo, Verona (San Zeno), Vicenza, Villa Valmarana
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 2, July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 134-135)
    Vicenza, Milan Villa Valmarana
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 3, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 136-137)
    Venice, Torcello [Rolls #33-34]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 4, July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 138-139)
    Ravenna, Urbino [Roll #34]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 5, July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 140-141)
    Gubbio, Perugia [Roll #34]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 6, July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 142-143)
    Perugia, Orvieto, Pitiglisur, Percola (inaug. of pool), Picnic [Roll #35]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 7, [July 1966] (Box 13, Folder 144-145)
    Unidentified [picnic at Roma]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 8, July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 146-147)
    Tarquinia, Rome et Vale! [Roll #35]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 9, July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 148-149)
    Laudot, Bellay, Seysse (Rhon), Solutré, Corcelles (ancien St. Laumar) [Roll #36]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 10 (Box 13, Folder 150-151)
    [family]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 11, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 152)
    Gwen's last visit - August, shipping cattle to Italy - September [Roll #36]
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 12, June 1966 (Box 13, Folder 153-154)
    La Bouree at work
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 13, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    [family Christmas 1966], Doughereyn Manor 1967, Reston 67
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 13, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 156)
    Defera Nursery 67, Defera Nursery summer 1967, Defera spray 67
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 14, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 15, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 158)
    Dido 9/67, Szklinski truck unloading auto ory. [sp?], Vidal 9/67, picking crew at Manor 9/67, Bellamy - hawk 9/67
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 16, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 159)
    Vidal 9/67, Dr. Frank Fall 1967, Fall 1967, flying over Boordy 9/67, hawk
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 17, Fall 1967 (Box 13, Folder 160)
    Mayers, Miner spray 1968
  - From Photo Album 3 [largest album], p. 17, Fall 1967 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - From box labeled France April 1937, September 1936 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Mommsin, P. W., & prop. near Macon, Macon
  - From box labeled France April 1937, September 1936 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Macon
  - From box labeled France April 1937 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Paris Lunch with Werth (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - H[otel] d'Angleterre, Biere - accident mainterm 9/36 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Pl[ace] de la Concorde, September 1936 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - From box labeled France April 1937 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Paris - R. Jacob
  - Lunch - Marne - near Sillery (Champs) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Rheims (rain) 9/36 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Vineyards and winery near Epernay (city?), September 1936 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - From box labeled France April 1937 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    vintage at Marsillarques
  - Winery & scales Marsillarques (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Marsillarques (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Gypsies in the Camargue, picnic in the Jura Mountains, September 1936 (Box 14, Folder 5)